{
    "subject": "resource/Julie_Andrews",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Best_Actress_Academy_Award_winners",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Julie Andrews is Best Actress Academy Award winners.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9469862580299377,
            "question": "Is Julie Andrews an Academy Award winner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.94395911693573,
            "question": "When did Julie Andrews win her Best Actress Academy Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9313082098960876,
            "question": "Which movie earned Julie Andrews the Best Actress Academy Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8596561551094055,
            "question": "In what category did Julie Andrews win an award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.859258234500885,
            "question": "What award did Julie Andrews win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7248400449752808,
            "question": "Has Julie Andrews won any other significant awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6999664902687073,
            "question": "Who is Julie Andrews?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5141188502311707,
            "question": "What is Julie Andrews known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40145060420036316,
            "question": "What films has Julie Andrews starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21238496899604797,
            "question": "What year was Julie Andrews born?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Julie Andrews is Best Actress Academy Award winners.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7167_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What films has Julie Andrews starred in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7167_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Julie Andrews known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7167_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Julie Andrews?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7167_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7167_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided indeed mention several instances where Julie Andrews won the Best Actress Academy Award, supporting the statement that the subject of these documents is Best Actress Academy Award winners."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}